whitestuff.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy | White Stuff

White Stuff Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us through our website at www.whitestuff.com ("our Site") will be processed, used and disclosed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

By using our Site, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy and to have your personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, processed in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

##  Who We Are

This website is owned and operated by White Stuff Limited, a company registered in England and Wales (company registration number 2319237) whose registered office is at Canterbury Court, Kennington Park, 1 - 3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE, United Kingdom. Our registered VAT number is GB974972851.

##  Information We May Collect From You

While most of the information we collect from you when you visit the Site does not personally identify you, there are a number of services that can only be made available if you provide us with certain information about you. We may collect and process the following personal information about you, depending on the services you use on the Site:

_Order processing:_ When you place an order with us on our Site, we ask for your name, address, delivery address, email address, contact number and payment information. We keep a record of this information so that we can recognise you and fulfil any orders you place with us.

_Customer care:_ If you contact us, we may keep a record of any correspondence you send us and, in common with lots of organizations, in order to maintain high standards of customer service, we record, and sometimes play back for training purposes, incoming telephone calls.

_Registration information:_ If you register on our site, for example, to place an order, or because you wish to subscribe to certain services that we provide, you are required to provide certain contact information including your name, e-mail address, phone number and address. We use this to contact you for matters relating to your orders, or to provide services that you have chosen to subscribe to such as to receive our newsletters or when you report a problem with our site and/or your order.

_Job applications:_ If you wish to apply online for a job position with us, you will be required to submit relevant information about your background and experience.

_Events, competitions or promotions:_ If you have elected to participate in an event, competition or promotion sponsored by us, we may ask you for certain information including your name, age, sex, address and email.

_Surveys:_ If you have elected to participate in our surveys, we may from time to time ask you to complete information that we use for research purposes. You do not have to respond to these surveys and may opt out of future emails by clicking a link at the bottom of the email or emailing us at [customercare@whitestuff.com](mailto:customercare@whitestuff.com), by notifying us in writing at Customer Care, White Stuff Limited, Canterbury Court, Kennington Park, 1 - 3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE, UK, or by calling us on 020 3752 5360.

_Website Use:_ Details of your visits to our site and the calls that you make to us including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

WE WILL ONLY EVER ASK YOU TO PROVIDE YOUR CREDIT CARD DETAILS IF YOU ARE PLACING AN ORDER WITH US. WE NEVER ASK FOR YOUR CREDIT CARD DETAILS BY EMAIL OR TEXT MESSAGE.

Our collection of the information provided above may involve the use of cookies. Please see the "Cookies" section below for more information.

##  Cookies

We may automatically collect website use information when you visit our Site, including where available your shortened IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and affiliates and to audit the use of our Site. This is anonymous statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not personally identify any individual.

In addition cookies are used. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer when you visit a website. If you visit the website again, it is recognised as a repeat visit by means of the cookie. The cookie contains a unique number and therefore no personal data. We will not use the cookie to identify you personally. The cookie cannot be used to identify you on websites of third parties. You can configure your web browser to refuse cookies, to delete cookies, or to be informed if a cookie is set. You can find out how to do this by clicking "help" on your browser menu. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, it may affect certain features or services on our Site.

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, data partners, advertisers and affiliates, or to third-party social media sites such as Facebook and Twitter. These third-parties may place their own cookies or other technological devices on your Internet browser. We have no control over these third parties and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for third-party policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

##  Where We Store Your Personal Data

The personal information you provide through the Site is processed in the United Kingdom. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), but only for the purposes as described in this Privacy Policy. It may also be processed by staff (see disclosure section below) operating outside the EEA who work on our behalf or for one of our suppliers.

All of these third parties act on our behalf and are contractually obligated to not collect, use or disclose the personal information for any purpose other than to perform such functions on our behalf or to provide services to us or as otherwise required by law. We take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy and under applicable data protection legislation.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

##  Uses Made of Your Information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To carry out our commercial obligations with you e.g. when you place an order on our Site.
  * To make your shopping experience with us as quick and efficient as possible.
  * To provide you with White Stuff offers, promotions, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * We share anonymised customer data with third party service providers to help us understand our customer's purchasing and browsing habits, which we then use to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.
  * Where you have provided explicit consent, we may permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you.

If you do not wish to receive the above mentioned marketing from us, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails or by contacting us by email at [customercare@whitestuff.com](mailto:customercare@whitestuff.com) or by notifying us in writing at Customer Care, White Stuff Limited, Canterbury Court, Kennington Park, 1 - 3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE, UK.

##  Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries for the purposes as described in this Privacy Policy.

Below is a list of White Stuff companies.

  * White Stuff Limited
  * White Stuff Group Limited
  * White Stuff Foundation Limited
  * White Stuff (Germany) GmbH

In addition we disclose the information described above for the performance of our contract with you, for example, with our payment service provider or delivery service provider.

##  Your Access Rights

In accordance with applicable data protection legislation, you have the right to access information held about you. Where entitled to do so, we may charge you an appropriate sum to reflect the cost of providing such information. If you would like a copy of the personal information held about you please contact us by email at [customercare@whitestuff.com](mailto:customercare@whitestuff.com) or by notifying us in writing at Customer Care, White Stuff Limited, Canterbury Court, Kennington Park, 1 - 3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE, UK. If you believe that any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or e-mail us as soon as possible.

##  Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.

##  Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Customer Care, White Stuff Limited, Canterbury Court, Kennington Park, 1 - 3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE, UK.

(Updated 08/12/2015)
